Contact

rohanmishra7598@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rohan-mishra-14ab7017b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Quiz
Public Relations
Public Speaking

Rohan Mishra

Civil undergraduate from NIT, Raipur. Structural Intern at TOGGLE Industries Inc, USA Training and placement Convener Raipur

Summary

Experienced Placement Coordinator with a demonstrated history of working in the higher education industry. Skilled in Quiz, Public Speaking, Acoustic Guitar, Time Management, and Public Relations. Strong human resources professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Civil Engineering from Nit raipur.

Experience

National Institute of Technology Training and Placement Co-ordinator August 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month) Chhattisgarh

Sahyog-The mentorship club 1 year 4 months

Core Mentor May 2019 - August 2019 (4 months)

Mentor May 2018 - May 2019 (1 year 1 month) chhattisgarh

Naya Raipur Development Authority Summer Trainee May 2019 - June 2019 (2 months) chhattisgarh

shubhkamna construction winter trainee November 2017 - December 2017 (2 months)

Education

Nit raipur

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Civil Engineering · (2017 - 2021)

BSP Senior Secondary School Sector 10

· (2012 - 2016)